https://www.campbellsville.edu/privacy-policy/

Current
TigernetCampus SafetyEmailMoodleLibraryFaculty DirectoryAcademic Calendar
Prospective
Admission & AidApply NowProgramsRequest InfoVisit CUPriority Registration
What kind of Tiger are you? CU offers many degree programs catered to the kind of Tiger you are. Are you a high schooler, dual credit student, a transfer, international, military student or adult learner? See how you can find your calling at CU. Learn More
Daily Health Assessment
Parents
Admission & AidAbout CampbellsvilleCampus MapCommencement
Campus SafetyAcademic CalendarBarnes and Noble Campus BookstoreVisit Us
Tiger Parents & Family You entrust us to offer safety and guidance to your child on their journey to find their calling. When your child joins the Campbellsville family, so do you. You can learn about what we offer at CU with the links above.
Faculty/Staff
EmailMoodleTigerNetAcademic AffairsAcademic CalendarCareers
Daily Health AssessmentCovid-19 Self-ReportingC.A.R.E PlanCampus MapOffice of PresidentThe Campbellsville Review
Faculty/Staff Directory
Make a Difference At CU, we want you to make a difference in our students’ lives. CU is located in Campbellsville, a vibrant town with a growing community in the middle of Kentucky. See our employment opportunities.
Alumni
Alumni & FriendsGiving OpportunitiesAlumni Association
Big Maroon Golf ScrambleAlumni CalendarCampbellsvillian Alumni Magazine
Homecoming 2020
Alumni, Welcome Home! Whether you earned your stripes as a Campbellsville student or made your Tiger name known through your contributions to our school, cause, and community, we are proud to have you as a part of our family. Follow us for updates on Facebook.
Event Calendars
Upcoming EventsStudent LifeCareer Services Events
Academic CalendarAlumni & Friends Events
Hear Our Roar! Join us as we cheer on our CU Tiger student-athletes! View our Athletics calendar.
Return to campus for classes
Covid-19 Info
Request Info
Visit
Apply
Search
MENUMENUAcademics
Academic Programs
Find Your Calling
CU offers more than 90 degree programs in multiple areas catered to the kind of Tiger you are.
View Our Programs
Online Programs
With 54 degrees available, Campbellsville offers a wide selection of online programs that are tailored to your career path.
Associates
Bachelors
Masters
Certificates
Academic Affairs
Academic SupportAccreditationCampbellsville ReviewCatalogCatalog Archive 2008-2018Cheatham CenterCommencement
Course OfferingsGeneral Education RequirementsMontgomery LibraryStudent AchievementStudent RecordsVeterans’ Services
Academic Support
Schools and Colleges
Arts and SciencesBarberingBusiness, Economics, and TechnologyCosmetologyCU RISE (Evening/Weekend)Education
MusicNursingOnlineSocial WorkTheology
View Our Programs
Request Info
Visit
Apply
Professional and Certificate Programs
Allied Health CareersBarbering CertificateCosmetology CertificateCU Expand CertificatesKids CollegeLicensed Practical Nursing
Limited Medical RadiographyWelding CertificateHVAC TechnologyIntroduction to Critical ThinkingPersonal CreativityCreativity in Teams and Organizations
View Our Programs
International Education
Center for Global EngagementEnglish as a Second LanguageStudy AbroadLouisville International Student Services (ISS)
ESL
Study Abroad
Louisville
Academic Calendar
About Our Academic Calendar
Campbellsville University’s academic calendar runs August 1 through July 31.
View Our Calendar to Learn More
View Our Programs
Request Info
Visit
Apply
Regional
Casey County
Casey County Education Center
Liberty, Ky.
Take individual classes that count toward a Liberal Arts and Sciences degree, earn an Allied Health certificate, and receive financial aid and work ready scholarships.
Learn More
Clinton County
Clinton College & Career Center
Albany, Ky.
Preparing Students for College, a Career, and Life, CU offers a range of Allied Health technical programs.
Learn More
Elizabethtown
Elizabethtown Instructional Site
Elizabethtown, Ky.
Offering undergraduate programs in Interdisciplinary Early Childhood Education (IECE) and Early Childhood Education (ECE).
Learn More
Harrodsburg
Harrodsburg Conover Education Center
Harrodsburg, Ky.
The Conover Center is committed to providing a Christ-centered, high quality educational experience by locating and retaining highly qualified and credentialed instructors.
Learn MoreAthletics
Hodgenville
Hodgenville Brockman Education Center
Hodgenville, Ky.
The Brockman Center is fully equipped with all of the tools and equipment you need to prepare for your professional career in Allied Health or Cosmetology.
Learn More
Los Angeles
Los Angeles Education Center
Los Angeles, Ca.
Los Angeles Education Center boasts its Marriage and Family Therapy Masters Program.
Learn More
Louisville
Louisville Education Center
Louisville, Ky.
With two locations in Louisville, Ky., CU Louisville boasts several degree options and certifications, including the Master of Science in Information Technology Management.
Learn More
Owensboro
Owensboro Instructional Site
Owensboro, Ky.
Receive quality educational preparation for successful transition to student teaching, K-TIP, and educational institutions.
Learn More
Somerset
Somerset Noe Education Center
Somerset, Ky.
CU’s Noe Somerset Education Center offers adult learners an accelerated program where classes are available both day and night, Monday-Friday.
Learn MoreAthletics
Admission & Aid
Apply Now
Are you ready to become a Campbellsville Tiger?
The first step to joining Campbellsville’s passion-driven, faith-focused community is to apply!
Apply Now
Visit Us
Main Campus Virtual TourPersonal VisitPreview DayTiger Take Over
Visit Us!
Preview Day
Tiger Take Over
Financial Aid
Sources of AidApplying for AidFinancial Aid FAQsNet Price CalculatorCollege NavigatorGlossary of Terms
Gainful Employment DisclosuresStudent EmploymentPolicies and ProceduresFinancial Aid Staff
View Our Scholarships and Grants
Tuition and Fees
Campbellsville
Regional Centers
Online Degrees
Technical and Trade
Courses and Other
Scholarships and Grants
Lending a Helping Hand
Learn more about what scholarships and grants we offer!
Scholarships and Grants
Church-Related Scholarships
Dual Credit
Dual Credit for High School Students
CU partners with over 30 high schools to offer qualified high school students the opportunity to enroll in CU courses for college credit.
Learn More
Military and Veterans
Serving Those Who Serve
Whether you are actively serving, in the reserves, are a veteran, or a military family member, we are very proud you are considering Campbellsville University and thank you for considering us.
Learn More
Tiger Life
Tiger Life
Live the Life of a Tiger
When you choose CU, you’re choosing to be more than a student, an athlete, or a Christian. You’re choosing to be a Tiger. And at Campbellsville, that means belonging.
Learn More
10,000
Students
35
Clubs and Organizations
28
Sports Teams
2
Nearby Nature Centers
Campus Ministry
Find Your Faith
Here at Campbellsville, it is our goal to provide you with a broad range of faith-oriented opportunities so you not only stay resolute in your faith, but grow in it.
Learn More
Baptist Campus MinistryChapelFellowship of Christian AthletesMission TripsCU Crew – Summer MinistryThe Vine
Student Life
Clubs and OrganizationsIntramural SportsStudent ActivitiesStudent Government Association
Campus Resources
Campus SafetyDining ServicesEmail-Faculty & StaffEmail-StudentsFaculty/Staff DirectoryFacilities DirectoryInformation Technology
Moodle AccessSnow Schedule
Student Services
Career ServicesCounseling ServicesTiger Health Clinic
Career Services
Counseling Services
Tiger Health Clinic
Barnes and Noble Campus Bookstore
Barnes and Noble Bookstore Home
Campus Life Calendar
Campbellsville Student events, intramural sports, movies, concerts, workshops and more.
View Our Calendar
Outreach
Church Outreach
Christ Centered, Church Connected, Changed Lives
Students advancing the Kingdom Of God.
Learn More
Church Outreach
Book a Student Team
Calendar
Kingdom Advance Network
Clay Hill Memorial Forest
Education and Research for Students
Promoting conservation by increasing public awareness of the importance of forests
Learn More
Community
Community
Learn about Campbellsville, Taylor County, downtown and area attractions around CU.
Learn More
Economic Impact Study
Campbellsville University’s annual economic impact across Kentucky
Learn More
Summer Camps and Conferences
Camps and Conferences
CU provides a Christian atmosphere where groups can come to our campus, use our facilities, and have fun.
Learn More
About
Careers
Make a Difference in Our Students’ Lives
At CU, we want you to make a difference in our students’ lives. CU is located in Campbellsville, Ky., a vibrant town with a growing community.
Employment Opportunities
Contact Us
If you have questions about CU, scheduling a visit, student information, regional locations, financial aid, or anything else, please contact us.
Learn More
Media
WLCU – TV/FMBroadcast ServicesUniversity CommunicationsSnow Schedule
University NewsNews ArchivesCU Style Guide
News
Telling the CU Story
CU News Archives
Office of President
Algernon Sydney Sullivan AwardBoard of TrusteesMission and ValuesPresident’s Biography
Rankings and AccoladesVice PresidentsVision 2025Women’s Alliance
Athletics
Campbellsville
CU Athletics is More Than a Game
Learn More  Schedule
Athletic Calendar
CU Sports Network
News Headlines
Watch Live and On Demand
Intramural Sports - Campbellsville
Compete against your fellow students and have a blast with your buddies!
Learn More
Academics
Academic Programs
Online Programs
Academic Affairs
Academic Support
Accreditation
Campbellsville Review
School of Business, Economics, and Technology
CU RISE (Evening/Weekend)
School of Education
School of Music
School of Nursing
Online Education
Carver School of Social Work
School of Theology
International Education
Study Abroad
Privacy Policy
Campbellsville University is committed to safeguarding your privacy. Contact us at if you have any questions or problems regarding the use of your Personal Data and we will gladly assist you.
By using this site or/and our services, you consent to the Processing of your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.
Table of Contents
Definitions used in this Policy
Data protection principles we follow
What rights do you have regarding your Personal Data
What Personal Data we gather about you
How we use your Personal Data
Who else has access to your Personal Data
How we secure your data
Information about cookies
Viewing or deleting your data
Contact information
Definitions
Personal Data – any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.
Processing – any operation or set of operations which is performed on Personal Data or on sets of Personal Data.
Data subject – a natural person whose Personal Data is being Processed.
Child – a natural person under 16 years of age.
We/us (either capitalized or not) –
Data Protection Principles
We promise to follow the following data protection principles:
Processing is lawful, fair, transparent. Our Processing activities have lawful grounds. We always consider your rights before Processing Personal Data. We will provide you information regarding Processing upon request.
Processing is limited to the purpose. Our Processing activities fit the purpose for which Personal Data was gathered.
Processing is done with minimal data. We only gather and Process the minimal amount of Personal Data required for any purpose.
Processing is limited with a time period. We will not store your personal data for longer than needed.
We will do our best to ensure the accuracy of data.
We will do our best to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of data.
Data Subject’s rights
The Data Subject has the following rights:
Right to information – meaning you have to right to know whether your Personal Data is being processed; what data is gathered, from where it is obtained and why and by whom it is processed.
Right to access – meaning you have the right to access the data collected from/about you. This includes your right to request and obtain a copy of your Personal Data gathered.
Right to rectification – meaning you have the right to request rectification or erasure of your Personal Data that is inaccurate or incomplete.
Right to erasure – meaning in certain circumstances you can request for your Personal Data to be erased from our records.
Right to restrict processing – meaning where certain conditions apply, you have the right to restrict the Processing of your Personal Data.
Right to object to processing – meaning in certain cases you have the right to object to Processing of your Personal Data, for example in the case of direct marketing.
Right to object to automated Processing – meaning you have the right to object to automated Processing, including profiling; and not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated Processing. This right you can exercise whenever there is an outcome of the profiling that produces legal effects concerning or significantly affecting you.
Right to data portability – you have the right to obtain your Personal Data in a machine-readable format or if it is feasible, as a direct transfer from one Processor to another.
Right to lodge a complaint – in the event that we refuse your request under the Rights of Access, we will provide you with a reason as to why. If you are not satisfied with the way your request has been handled please contact us.
Right for the help of supervisory authority – meaning you have the right for the help of a supervisory authority and the right for other legal remedies such as claiming damages.
Right to withdraw consent – you have the right withdraw any given consent for Processing of your Personal Data.
Data we gather
Information you have provided us with
This might be your e-mail address, name, billing address, home address, etc. – mainly information that is necessary for contacting you. We save the information you provide us with in order for us to contact you regarding admission to the university, employment opportunities, newsletters, and more. This information includes, for example, your name and e-mail address.
Information automatically collected about you
This includes information that is automatically stored by cookies and other session tools. For example, your IP address, your general location, etc. This information is used to improve the website and our students’ experience. When you use our services or look at the contents of our website, your activities may be logged.
Information from our partners
We gather information from our trusted partners with confirmation that they have legal grounds to share that information with us. This is either information you have provided them directly with or that they have gathered about you on other legal grounds. See the list of our partners here.
Publicly available information
We might gather information about you that is publicly available.
How we use your Personal Data
We use your Personal Data in order to:
provide our service to you. This includes, for example, providing you with other products and services that you have requested; providing you with promotional items at your request and communicating with you in relation to those products and services; communicating and interacting with you; and notifying you of changes to any services.
enhance your customer experience;
fulfill an obligation under law or contract;
contact you.
We use your Personal Data on legitimate grounds and/or with your Consent.
On the grounds of entering into a contract or fulfilling contractual obligations, we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:
to identify you;
to provide you a service or to send/offer you a product;
to communicate either for sales or invoicing;
and to contact you regarding admission to the university.
On the ground of legitimate interest, we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:
to send you personalized emails* (from us and/or our carefully selected partners);
to administer and analyze our client base (behavior and history) in order to improve the quality, variety, and availability of products/ services offered/provided;
to conduct questionnaires concerning client satisfaction.
As long as you have not informed us otherwise, we consider offering you products/services that are similar or same to your purchasing history/browsing behavior to be our legitimate interest.
With your consent we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:
to send you newsletters and campaign offers (from us and/or our carefully selected partners);
for other purposes we have asked your consent for;
to contact you.
We Process your Personal Data in order to fulfill obligation rising from law and/or use your Personal Data for options provided by law. We reserve the right to anonymize Personal Data gathered and to use any such data. We will use data outside the scope of this Policy only when it is anonymized. We save your billing information and other information gathered about you for as long as needed for accounting purposes or other obligations deriving from law, but not longer than one year.
We might process your Personal Data for additional purposes that are not mentioned here, but are compatible with the original purpose for which the data was gathered. To do this, we will ensure that:
the link between purposes, context and nature of Personal Data is suitable for further Processing;
the further Processing would not harm your interests and
there would be appropriate safeguard for Processing.
We will inform you of any further Processing and purposes.
Who else can access your Personal Data
We do not share your Personal Data with strangers. Personal Data about you is in some cases provided to our trusted partners in order to either make providing the service to you possible or to enhance your customer experience. We share your data with:
Our processing partners:
The Learning House, Mindscape Solutions, and Summit Media.
Our business partners:
The Learning House
Connected third parties:
Constant Contact Email Marketing
We only work with Processing partners who are able to ensure adequate level of protection to your Personal Data. We disclose your Personal Data to third parties or public officials when we are legally obliged to do so. We might disclose your Personal Data to third parties if you have consented to it or if there are other legal grounds for it.
How we secure your data
We do our best to keep your Personal Data safe.  We use safe protocols for communication and transferring data (such as HTTPS). We use anonymizing and pseudonymising where suitable. We monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks.
Even though we try our best we can not guarantee the security of information. However, we promise to notify suitable authorities of data breaches. We will also notify you if there is a threat to your rights or interests. We will do everything we reasonably can to prevent security breaches and to assist authorities should any breaches occur.
If you have an account with us, note that you have to keep your username and password secret.
Children
We do not intend to collect or knowingly collect information from children. We do not target children with our services.
Cookies and other technologies we use
We use cookies and/or similar technologies to analyses customer behavior, administer the website, track users’ movements, and to collect information about users. This is done in order to personalize and enhance your experience with us.
A cookie is a tiny text file stored on your computer. Cookies store information that is used to help make sites work. Only we can access the cookies created by our website. You can control your cookies at the browser level. Choosing to disable cookies may hinder your use of certain functions.
We use cookies for the following purposes:
Necessary cookies – these cookies are required for you to be able to use some important features on our website, such as logging in. These cookies don’t collect any personal information.
Functionality cookies – these cookies provide functionality that makes using our service more convenient and makes providing more personalized features possible. For example, they might remember your name and e-mail in comment forms so you don’t have to re-enter this information next time when commenting.
Analytics cookies – these cookies are used to track the use and performance of our website and services
Advertising cookies – these cookies are used to deliver advertisements that are relevant to you and to your interests. In addition, they are used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. They are usually placed to the website by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. These cookies remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organizations such as advertisers. Often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organization.
You can remove cookies stored in your computer via your browser settings. Alternatively, you can control some 3rd party cookies by using a privacy enhancement platform such as optout.aboutads.info or youronlinechoices.com. For more information about cookies, visit allaboutcookies.org.
We use Google Analytics to measure traffic on our website. Google has their own Privacy Policy which you can review here. If you’d like to opt out of tracking by Google Analytics, visit the Google Analytics opt-out page.
Viewing or deleting your data
If you would like to view or delete your data collected from this website, go to our Privacy Tools page. For all other inquiries, contact ampavy@campbellsville.edu.
Contact Information
800-264-6014, admissions@campbellsville.edu
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to make change to this Privacy Policy.
Last modification was made May 25, 2018.
Request Info
Visit
Apply
1 University Drive
Campbellsville,
KY
42718
(800) 264-6014
Email Us!
(270) 789-5142
(fax)
